Edward Livingston Papers, 1683-1877 (bulk 1764-1836 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 1: Edward Livingston (1764-1836), 1781-1877; 1781-1836; 94 boxes
  - Subseries 1A: Correspondence, 1784-1836; 56 boxes
    - General, 1784-1836; 45 boxes
      - Summersett, James, 1806; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Sumner, William H., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Sumter, Thomas, 1802-1803; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Sumter, Thomas, Jr., 1802; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Sumter, Mrs. Thomas de Delage, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Sutton, D.I., 1827; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Swartwout, John, 1802-1806; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Swartwout, Samuel, 1783-1856, 1831-1834; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Sypher, Samuel, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - S: Unidentified, 1797-1800; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Taillandier, A., 1797-1867, 1836; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Talcott and Bowers, undated; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Tallmadge, James, 1778-1853, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Tallmadge, N.P., 1836; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Taney, Roger Brooke, 1777-1864, 1831-1836; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Tappen, George, 1799; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Tappen, John, 1792-1796; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Targee, John, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Tayleur, Bates, and Chorley, 1822-1823; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Taylor, John Brickwood, 1805; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Taylor, John W., 1804; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Taylor, P., 1795; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Taylor, R., undated; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Tazewell, Littleton W., 1774-1860, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Teackle, Littleton Dennis, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Templeman, John, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Ten Broeck, Leonard, 1789; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Ternant, 1805-1814; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Thatcher, Lucy F. Knox, undated; 1 folder (Folder 58)
      - Thens, Thomas H., 1830-1834; 1 folder (Folder 59)
      - Thibaut, 1804; 1 folder (Folder 60)
      - Thibodaux, Bregite, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 61)
      - Thibodaux, H.S., 1769-1827, 1816-1826; 1 folder (Folder 62)
      - Thierry, undated; 1 folder (Folder 63)
      - Thomas, J.E., 1833-1834; 1 folder (Folder 72)
      - Thomas, Thomas, 1789-1801; 1 folder (Folder 64)
      - Thompson, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 65)
      - Thompson, J., 1822; 1 folder (Folder 66)
      - Thompson, Samuel H., 1828-1832; 1 folder (Folder 67)
      - Thompson, Smith, 1768-1843, 1794-1834; 1 folder (Folder 68)
      - Thompson, William, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 69)
      - Thompson, James, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 70)
      - Thompson, William, 1805; 1 folder (Folder 71)
      - Thorn, Herman, 1834-1835; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Thorne, 1834-1835; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Thornton, William, 1759-1826, 1818; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Throop, E.T., 1784-1874, 1831-1832; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Throop, Josiah, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Ticknor, George, 1791-1871, 1827-1829; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Tilghman, Benjamin, 1831-1832; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Tillary, James, 1801-1803; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Tillier, Rudolph, III, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Tillotson, Shulad, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Tocqueville, Alexis de, 1805-1859, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Tod and Romanes, 1827; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Todd, David L., 1822; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Tomkins, Daniel D., 1774-1825, 1803-1820; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Tornel, Jose Maria, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Tournillon, S.J., 1813-1828; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Tournon, Countess de, undated; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Towles, John, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Townsend, 1834-1835; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Townsley, Thomas F., 1824-1827; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Trask, J.E., 1804; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Treasury Department, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Trimble, Jacob, undated; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Trist, H.B., 1823; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Trist, Nicholas Philip, 1800-1874, 1823-1836; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Trouard, A., 1812-1813; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Troup, Robert, 1757-1832, 1788-1829; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Truxtun, Thomas, 1755-1822, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Tucker, A.B., 1822-1834; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Tucker, Benjamin, 1813; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Tucker, Benjamin, Jr., 1804; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Tucker, Henry, 1780-1848, undated; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Tureaud, A.D., 1820-1822; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Turnbull, Charles, 1791; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Turner, E., 1778-1860, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Turner, F.L., 1813-1834; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Turner, H., 1805; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Turner, Seth, 1795-1803; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - U.S. Bank, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Ulrick, H., 1829; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Uriell, Patrick, 1804-1807; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Ustick, William, Jr., 1796; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Vacher, Francis, 1806; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Vail, Aaron, 1796-1878, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Vail, Aaron, 1796-1878, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Vail, Aaron, 1796-1878, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Vail, Aaron, 1796-1878, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Vail, Eugene A., 1832-1836; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Van Alen, Peter, 1791; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Van Amringe, W.F., 1834; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Van Arlen, John, undated; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Van Benthuysen, John, 1793-1795; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862, 1828-1829; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Van Buren, Smith, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Van Cortlandt, Philip, 1749-1831, 1789-1807; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Van Cortlandt, Pierre, Jr., 1762-1848, 1794; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Van Den Broek, R.J., 1797; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Van Der Kemp, F.A., 1752-1829, 1791; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Van Gaasbeek, Peter, 1786-1792; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Van Keuren, Garret, 1826-1835; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Van Loon, Polly, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Van Ness, Anne, 1813; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Van Ness, C.P., 1782-1852, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Van Ness, Eugene, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Van Ness, Jacob, 1800-1829; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Van Ness, John P., 1792; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Van Ness, W.P., 1778-1826, 1800-1825; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Van Rensselaer, Henry J., 1789; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Van Rensselaer, Jacob Rutsen, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Van Rensselaer, Jeremiah, 1792-1795; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Van Rensselaer, K.K., 1833; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Van Rensselaer, K.R., 1790-1792; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Van Rensselaer, Solomon, 1774-1852, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Van Rensselaer, Stephen, 1764-1839, 1813-1834; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Van Schaak, Peter, 1747-1832, 1790-1794; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Van Scholter, P., 1829; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Van Schoonhoven, G., 1792-1794; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Van Valkenburg, Bartholemew J., 1817-1825; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Van Vechten, Abraham, 1762-1837, 1793-1800; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Van Vleek, Catherine, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Van Zandt, Peter, 1797; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Vanbercy, E.M. Farmar, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Vanderburgh, James, 1789; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Vanderlyn, J., 1776-1852, 1827; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Vanuxem and Lombaert, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Varick, Richard, 1753-1831, 1801; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Varnum, Joseph B., 1810; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Vaughan, Charles R., 1774-1849, 1825-1833; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Vaughan, John, 1826-1834; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Vaux, Roberts, 1786-1836, 1823-1828; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Vaux, Roberts, 1786-1836, 1831-1835; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Verplanck, Gulian C., 1786-1870, 1825-1828; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Verplanck, Philip, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Verry, Goullier, 1805; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Vidal (1), 1806; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Vidal (2), 1812; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Vidal, Josephine, 1811; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Vidauvre, M.L., 1828; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Vidua, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Viel Castille, undated; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Villar, 1807; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Villavaso, N.T. de, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Villere, James, 1761-1830, 1821-1824; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Villeroi, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Vinot, S., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Visscher, M., 1789; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Visscher, Sebastian, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Vorter, A., 1834; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Vosburgh, Martin, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - V: Unidentified, 1797-1815; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Waddell, William Coventry H., 1831-1832; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Wadsworth, James, 1768-1844, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Waggaman, George A., 1782-1843, 1823-1824; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Waggaman, George A., 1782-1843, 1825-1833; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Waggaman, Thomas E., 1829; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Wagner, Peter K., 1824; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Wagner, Peter K., 1825; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Wagner, Peter K., 1826-1833; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Walker, R.J., 1801-1869, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Walker, Samuel P., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Wallenstein, 1831-1832; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Wallis, Joseph, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Wallis, Perly, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Waln, Jesse, 1830-1831; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Walsh, Robert, Jr., 1825-1836; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Walton, William, 1820; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Walworth, R. Hyde, 1788-1867, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Ward, Aaron, 1790-1867, 1831-1834; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Ward, John and Co., 1791; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Ward, Richard R., 1818-1828; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Ward, Townley, 1790-1791; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Warden, D.B., 1772-1845, 1806-1833; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Ware, N.A., 1833; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Washington, Jane C., 1833; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Washington, Thomas, 1824-1830; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Waters, Ramsay, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Watkins, John, 1804-1807; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Watson, James, 1790-1794; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Watson, John, 1813; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Watterson, George, 1783-1854, 1827-1834; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Watts, Charles, 1824-1826; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Watts, John, 1790-1803; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Weaver, Christopher, 1795; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Weaver, William A., 1833-1835; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Webb, James, 1828; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Webb, James Watson, 1802-1844, 1831-1832; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Webb, Samuel B., 1792; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Webster, Daniel, 1782-1852, 1825-1836; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Weems, James J., 1829; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Weight, Joseph, 1789; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Welles, undated; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Wendell, Henry, 1785; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Wendover, Stephen, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Wentz, Henri, 1834; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - West, Francis, 1791; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - West, John K., 1833; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - West, Nathaniel, Jr., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Wetherald, James, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Wheaton, Henry, 1785-1848, 1827-1835; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Wheeler, Solomon, 1807; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Wheeler, William, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Whetten, John, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Whipple, Oliver, 1811; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - White, Alexander A., 1819-1823; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - White, Campbell P., 1830; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - White, E.D., 1795-1847, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - White, Ellen Adair, undated; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - White, James, 1817; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - White, James W., 1836; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - White, John, 1788-1791; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - White, Joseph M., 1833-1834; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - White, Joseph, 1835-1836; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - White, Maunsel, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - White, Robert, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Whiting, Amos, 1817; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Whitney, Charles, 1799-1804; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Whitney, William Wallace, 1833-1835; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Whittemore, Bernard B., 1834-1836; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Whittle, Conway, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Whittlesey, Elisha, 1830-1833; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Whittlesey, Matthew B., 1801; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Wickham, John, 1763-1839, 1810; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Wickham, William, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Wikoff, William, Sr., 1805-1814; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Wikoff, William, Jr., 1823; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Wilde, Richard Henry, 1789-1847, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Wilkes, John, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Wilkins and Linton, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Wilkins, G.M., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Wilkins, Martin S., 1816-1820; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Wilkins, William, 1779-1865, 1835; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Wilkinson, C., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Willcocks, Williams, 1796-1799; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Willett, Marinus, 1740-1830, 1801; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Williams, Azarias, 1796; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Williams, Edward, 1791-1802; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Williams, Edwin, 1797-1854, 1833; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Williams, Elisha, 1773-1833, 1801; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Williams, Ezra, 1830-1832; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Williams, J.C., undated; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Williams, John, 1779-1837, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Williams, Micah, 1790; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Williams, Robert (I), 1798-1802; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Williams, Robert (2), 1816-1832; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - Williams, William D., 1796; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Williamson, J., 1812; 1 folder (Folder 58)
      - Willis, Lewis B., 1826-1827; 1 folder (Folder 59)
      - Willis, Perrin, 1821; 1 folder (Folder 60)
      - Willis, William, 1794; 1 folder (Folder 61)
      - Willis, Zipporah, 1831; 1 folder (Folder 62)
      - Williston, E.B., 1826-1827; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Wilson, G.K., 1831; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Wilson, Henry, 1826; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Wilson, Hugh, 1808; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Wilson, John, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Wilson, John B., 1808; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Wilson, Nathaniel, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Wilson, R.L., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Wilson, Stephen R., 1803; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Wilson, W., 1793-1801; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Winans, Stephen, 1789-1790; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Winchester, George, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Wind, P., 1796; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Winter, Gabriel, 1814-1820; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Winter, Joseph, 1805-1820; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Winter, Joseph S., 1819; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Wise, Francis, 1808; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Withers, Thomas J., 1826; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Wolcott, Oliver, 1760-1833, 1792; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Wolstonecraft, C., 1805-1816; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Wood, B., 1801-1803; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Wood, Samuel R., 1832; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Wood, William, 1829-1830; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Woodbury, Levi, 1789-1851, 1833-1836; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Woodrooff, C., 1818-1831; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Woodworth, John, 1793-1830; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Woolridge, Edmund, 1804; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Woolsey, George M., undated; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Woolsey, M.T., 1780-1838, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Woolsey, W.W., 1808-1818; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Wooster, Charles W., 1780-1748, 1813; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Worcester, Noah, 1758-1837, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Workman, James, 1808-1813; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Workman, James, 1815-1817; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Workman, James, 1822-1824; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Workman, James, 1825-1830; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Wreddington, 1815; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Wright, Augustus, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Wright, David (1), 1825-1826; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Wright, David (2), 1835; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Wright, John, 1816; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Wright, Samuel, 1790-1791; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Wurts, John, 1829; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Wyer, Edward, 1834-1835; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Wynans, James, 1789; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Wynkoop, H., 1792-1793; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Wynkoop, John C., 1789-1791; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - W: Unidentified, 1789-1834; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Yates, Peter Waldron, 1747-1826, 1786-1892; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Yates, Peter Waldron, 1747-1826, 1793-1794; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Yates, Peter Waldron, 1747-1826, 1795-1798; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Ybanez, Fernandez, 1811; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Yberville, 1822; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Young, Bethia, 1803; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Young, Joseph, 1810; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Young, Samuel C., 1818-1820; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Young, Susanna, 1820; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Young, Thomas, 1800-1801; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Young, Townley W., 1824; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Young, William (1), 1817-1818; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Young, William (2), 1819; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Yrujo, L Chevalier de, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Yznardi, Maria, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Zaizer, J., 1824; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Zavala, Lorenzo de, 1836; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Unidentified: Edward Livingston to Others, 1798; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Unidentified: Edward Livingston to Others, 1802; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Unidentified: Edward Livingston to Others, undated; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Unidentified: To Edward Livingston, undated; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Unidentified: To Edward Livingston, undated; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous Enclosures and Copies, 1783-1835; 1 folder (Folder 23)
    - Family, 1784-1836; 11 boxes
      Family correspondents include all persons with the surname Livingston, immediate relations, and any others who can be identified as family by their greeting or the content of their letter(s). Other surnames one can expect to find here include Armstrong, Barton, Davezac, Garrettson, Lewis, McEvers, Montgomery, and Tillotson.
      - Armstrong, Alida Livingston, 1761-1822 (Sister), 1804-1822; 6 folders (Folder 1-6)
      - Armstrong, John, 1758-1843 (Brother-in-Law), 1794-1833; 4 folders (Folder 7-10)
      - Armstrong, John Jr., 1824-1834; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Armstrong, Robert Livingston, 1830; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Barton, Coralie Livingston, 1806-1873 (Daughter), 1817-1831; 14 folders (Folder 1-14)
      - Barton, Thomas Pennant, 1803-1869, 1832-1835; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Davezac, Armand, undated; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Davezac, Auguste, 1780-1851 (Brother-in-Law), 1805-1835; 13 folders (Folder 2-14)
      - Davezac, Auguste Jr., 1828; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Davezac, Edward Livingston, undated; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Davezac, Gaston, 1824; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Davezac, Jules, 1827-1830; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Davezac de Castera, 1809; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Davezac de Castera, M. (Mother-in-Law), 1805; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Garretson, Catherine Livingston, 1752-1849 (Sister), 1787-1834; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Garretson, Freeborn, 1752-1827 (Brother-in-Law), 1833; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Garretson, Freeborn, Jr., 1818; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Garretson, Mary Rutherford, -1879, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Jones, William, 1777-1812, 1803-1811; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - McEvers, Bache (Nephew), 1823; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Lewis, Morgan, 1754-1844 (Brother-in-Law), 1784-1834; 6 folders (Folder 7-12)
      - Livingston, A?, 1832; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Livingston, Alexander, 1793; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Livingston, Anne H. Shippen (Sister-in-Law), 1800-1822; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Livingston, Beekman, 1836; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Livingston, Henry Brockholst, 1757-1823 (2nd cousin), 1790-1815; 2 folders (Folder 17-18)
      - Livingston, Charles Edward, 1790-1802 (Son), 1797-1802; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Livingston, Charles L., 1830-1833; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Livingston, Edward P., 1779-1843 (Cousin), 1824-1833; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Livingston, George, 1800; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Livingston, Gilbert, 1801-1802; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Livingston, Gilbert R., 1791; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Livingston, Henry, 1788-1798; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Livingston, Henry Beekman, 1750-1831 (Brother), 1785-1831; 3 folders (Folder 26-28)
      - Livingston, Henry G., 1791-1799; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Livingston, Henry W., 1807; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Livingston, James, 1747-1832, 1802-1830; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Livingston, James Allen, 1825; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Livingston, Joanna, 1759-1829 (Sister), 1804-1812; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Livingston, John, 1814; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Livingston, John of "Oak Hill", 1750-1822, 1795-1810; 3 folders (Folder 35-37)
      - Livingston, John R., 1755-1851 and Eliza, -1848 (Brother- and Sister-in-Law), 1796-1834; 9 folders (Folder 1-9)
      - Livingston, John R., Jr. (Nephew), 1830-1835; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Livingston, Julia, 1794-1814, 7 folders (Folder 1-7)
      - Livingston, Julia, 1801-1882 (Niece), 1824; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Livingston, Lewis, 1798-1822, 1807-1821; 14 folders (Folder 9-22)
      - Livingston, Louise, 1781-1860, 1808-1831; 1 box
      - Livingston, Louise, 1781-1860, 1808-1830; 1 box
      - Livingston, MArgaret Beekman, 1724-1800 (Mother), 1789-1798; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Livingston, Margaret Beekman (Niece), 1796-1832; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Livingston, Mary McEvers, -1801 (Wife), 1791-1800; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Livingston, Maturin, 1769-1847 (Distant Cousin, Nephew by Marriage), 1795-1830; 4 folders (Folder 4-7)
      - Livingston, P., 1821-1822; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Livingston, Peter R., 1796-1798; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Livingston, Peter Van Brugh, circa 1824; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Livingston, Peter William, 1767-1826, 1801; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Livingston, Philip, 1815; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Livingston, Philip Henry, 1794; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Livingston, Philip J., 1796; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Livingston, Richard Montgomery, 1814-1818; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Livingston, Robert H., 1789; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Livingston, Robert J., 1794; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Livingston, Robert L. (1), 1798-1801; 1 folder (Folder 18)